export default {
    title: 'Useful Spanish Words | Español - Português',
    description: 'Spanish words available for free to beginners up to advanced users.',
    cards: [
      {
          front: 'donde',
          back: 'onde'
      },
      {
          front: 'como',
          back: 'como'
      },
      {
          front: 'mucho',
          back: 'muito'
      },
      {
          front: 'cuando',
          back: 'quando'
      },
      {
          front: 'ser',
          back: 'ser'
      },
      {
          front: 'estar',
          back: 'estar'
      },
      {
          front: 'hacer',
          back: 'fazer'
      },
      {
          front: 'haber',
          back: 'ter'
      },
      {
          front: 'bueno',
          back: 'bom'
      },
      {
          front: 'amigo',
          back: 'amigo'
      },
      {
          front: 'ir',
          back: 'ir'
      },
      {
          front: 'quién',
          back: 'quem'
      },
      {
          front: 'tener',
          back: 'ter'
      },
      {
          front: 'gracias',
          back: 'obrigada'
      },
      {
          front: 'por favor',
          back: 'por favor'
      },
      {
          front: 'poder',
          back: 'poder'
      },
      {
          front: 'gustar',
          back: 'gostar'
      },
      {
          front: 'de',
          back: 'de'
      },
      {
          front: 'ahora',
          back: 'agora'
      },
      {
          front: 'poner',
          back: 'pôr'
      },
      {
          front: 'venir',
          back: 'vir'
      },
      {
          front: 'chica',
          back: 'menina'
      },
      {
          front: 'chico',
          back: 'menino'
      },
      {
          front: 'para',
          back: 'para'
      },
      {
          front: 'hasta',
          back: 'até'
      },
      {
          front: 'porque',
          back: 'porque'
      },
      {
          front: 'El, la, los, las',
          back: 'o, a, os, as'
      },
      {
          front: 'antes',
          back: 'antes'
      },
      {
          front: 'más',
          back: 'mais'
      },
      {
          front: 'bien',
          back: 'bem'
      },
      {
          front: 'salir',
          back: 'sair'
      },
      {
          front: 'hola',
          back: 'olá'
      },
      {
          front: 'tú',
          back: 'você'
      },
      {
          front: 'o',
          back: 'ou'
      },
      {
          front: 'llevar',
          back: 'levar'
      },
      {
          front: 'si',
          back: 'se'
      },
      {
          front: 'Usted',
          back: 'você'
      },
      {
          front: 'deber',
          back: 'dever'
      },
      {
          front: 'muy',
          back: 'muito'
      },
      {
          front: 'bajo',
          back: 'baixo'
      },
      {
          front: 'todo',
          back: 'todo'
      },
      {
          front: 'mismo',
          back: 'mesmo'
      },
      {
          front: 'tanto',
          back: 'tanto'
      },
      {
          front: 'empezar',
          back: 'começar'
      },
      {
          front: 'sin',
          back: 'sem'
      },
      {
          front: 'conocer',
          back: 'conhecer'
      },
      {
          front: 'adiós',
          back: 'adeus'
      },
      {
          front: 'entender',
          back: 'entender'
      },
      {
          front: 'beber',
          back: 'beber'
      },
      {
          front: 'contento',
          back: 'feliz'
      },
      {
          front: 'siempre',
          back: 'sempre'
      },
      {
          front: 'escuchar',
          back: 'escutar'
      },
      {
          front: 'hombre',
          back: 'homem'
      },
      {
          front: 'nunca',
          back: 'nunca'
      },
      {
          front: 'yo',
          back: 'eu'
      },
      {
          front: 'sí',
          back: 'sim'
      },
      {
          front: 'grande',
          back: 'grande'
      },
      {
          front: 'también',
          back: 'também'
      },
      {
          front: 'comer',
          back: 'comer'
      },
      {
          front: 'mujer',
          back: 'mulher'
      },
      {
          front: 'otro',
          back: 'outro'
      },
      {
          front: 'decir',
          back: 'dizer'
      },
      {
          front: 'hora',
          back: 'hora'
      },
      {
          front: 'desde',
          back: 'desde'
      },
      {
          front: 'ver',
          back: 'ver'
      },
      {
          front: 'malo',
          back: 'mal'
      },
      {
          front: 'pensar',
          back: 'pensar'
      },
      {
          front: 'trabajar',
          back: 'trabalhar'
      },
      {
          front: 'nosotros',
          back: 'nós'
      },
      {
          front: 'entre',
          back: 'entre'
      },
      {
          front: 'durante',
          back: 'durante'
      },
      {
          front: 'creer',
          back: 'acreditar'
      },
      {
          front: 'echar',
          back: 'atirar'
      },
      {
          front: 'sacar',
          back: 'remover'
      },
      {
          front: 'cosa',
          back: 'coisa'
      },
      {
          front: 'primero',
          back: 'primeiro'
      },
      {
          front: 'encontrar',
          back: 'encontrar'
      },
      {
        front: 'leer',
        back: 'ler'
      },
    ]
};

